https://www.savortheband.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicySAVOR THE BAND recognizes that you care how information about you is used and shared and we respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the information we may collect from you, how we collect that information, how we use that information, and your choices with respect to how your information is collected and used. By using our website, mobile applications, or providing information to us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.This Privacy Policy was lasted updated March 2019 and may be updated from time to time. Please check back periodically for further updates and changes to the Privacy Policy. The most updated version will be available on our website.What information about me is collected & stored?Information Provided by YouWe collect and store information that you provide to us through our interactions with you, including through our websites, in our properties, through our customer service representatives, at events, through mobile applications, through marketing efforts, including contests, sweepstakes and events, and through third parties. We may also receive information about you from other brands within the SAVOR THE BAND family of brands.You may elect not to provide certain information, which could result in you not being able to take advantage of certain capabilities of this website, our mobile applications or other services we offer. For example, you must provide certain personal information in order to place an order or to register for an account on or through our website.We may request, collect and store some or all of the following types of personal information: your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, telephone number, financial and payment information, including your credit card number and expiration date, gender, personal interests, date of birth, and any information about a third party you provide when we ship an order. We may maintain a record of your product interest and purchases. If you access our website or mobile applications with your log-in credentials from a social networking site (e.g. Facebook, Pinterest, or Twitter) or if you otherwise agree to associate your account with us with a social networking site, we may receive personal information about you from such social networking site, in accordance with the terms of use and privacy policy of such social networking site. We may add this to the information we have already collected from you via other interactions.When you download or use our mobile applications, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services like local store information, search results, and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow users to disable location services by using controls located in the device’s settings menu. If you have questions about how to disable your device’s location services, please contact your mobile service carrier or your device manufacturer.Automatically Collected InformationWe collect and store certain other non-personally identifiable information automatically whenever you interact with us. For example, we may collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser information and reference site domain name when you visit this website. We may analyze this data for preferences, trends, and site usage statistics.We may also collect information by using cookies, web beacons, and related technologies in order to analyze and understand how the website is used and to improve your visits to the website. For example, we may use cookies and related technologies to: (i) customize account pages for you, (ii) track user visits and account features, (iii) determine what features and pages are most frequently requested or visited, and (iv) save your password so you do not have to provide it each time you visit the website.“Cookies” are small text files that a website sends to a user’s hard drive through the browser for data storage. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. By disabling or otherwise rejecting cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings on this website. We recommend that you leave cookies “turned on” so that we can offer you a better shopping experience on this website.We use third-party companies to provide Internet data hosting and to help us measure and determine how visitors use our website and to evaluate the effectiveness of our website and promotions so that we can improve and optimize our website and the products and services we offer. We use third-party companies to serve advertisements (banners or links) on our behalf throughout the Internet. These companies use tracking technologies (including cookies and pixel tags) to collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our website and your interactions with our products and services. This information helps third parties deliver tailored advertisements to you and others on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers throughout the Internet based on your interests and browsing of our website (remarketing). We use third-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) to better understand and advertise to audiences that visit our website. We do not use or associate personally identifiable information with remarketing lists, cookies, data feeds, or other anonymous identifiers.Our websites currently do not have a mechanism to recognize “Do Not Track” signals, but several of the third-party companies who utilize these cookies or beacons enable you to opt out of this advertising. If you wish to opt out of receiving this third-party interest-based advertising, you may obtain more information HERE. Please note this does not opt you out of receiving marketing communications from us.Some of our e-mail communications to you may include a “click-through URL” linked to a particular page on the website. By clicking on one of these URLs, you will automatically enter our website and we may collect information related to the “click-through.” You may avoid having this information collected by not clicking on URL links in our e-mail communications.We also use a variety of retail analytics tools in our stores for operational and marketing purposes, such as measuring and analyzing traffic patterns. These tools collect data from sensors, including video cameras, smartphone detectors, Wi-Fi networks, or other devices, to evaluate and improve your in-store experience.Information from Other SourcesWe may collect information about you from third-party sources and information that is publicly available. For example, information you submit in a public forum (e.g., a blog, chat room, or social network site) can be read, collected, or used by us and others, and could be used to personalize your experience. You are responsible for the information you choose to submit in these instances. Another example is that we may receive demographic information about you from a third party to make our service and marketing efforts more efficient and personalized for you.How is your information used?We use the personal information we collect to communicate with you, analyze and develop our business, and to improve our products, services, and interactions with customers. We, or third-party service providers we engage, may use the information to process and ship orders, provide products and services that you have ordered or requested, send order and shipping confirmations, provide customer service, respond to your comments, questions or complaints, personalize your interactions with us, identify your preferences and shopping habits, analyze trends and statistics, create, administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions, evaluate and improve the website and our products and services, and prepare and send you marketing communications and other information regarding our products, services or special events. We also use your information for business purposes such as security, legal compliance, payment processing, analytics, operations, fraud detection, reporting, and making back-ups.You always have the choice not to receive marketing communications. For instructions on opting out of those communications, please review below the section entitled “How Do I Indicate Whether or Not I Want to Receive Promotional Communications?”We display personal testimonials/reviews of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us https://www.savortheband.com/contact/With whom do we share this information?Except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, or share with third parties any of your personal information.We may share your personal information with other brands within the SAVOR THE BAND family of brands. We may share personal information with certain third parties that perform services on our behalf. The services provided by those third parties may include: operating or hosting the website, providing the products and services you request, authorization and processing of your payments, product fulfillment, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, marketing and promotional material distribution, loyalty program management, promotions fulfillment, web site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. Those third parties are not authorized to use or disclose personal information you provide to us on or through this website for any purpose other than to perform the services designated by us.We may share personal information with a third party if we are required by law to disclose that personal information. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal process. We may also disclose this information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or if we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate or address unlawful acts or acts that may endanger the health or safety of a consumer or the general public, to verify or enforce compliance with the terms of use and policies that govern our website or as otherwise required or permitted by law. In addition, the personal information you provide to us may be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale involving all or part of SAVOR THE BAND or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change of control.What about the privacy of children under 13?We do not intend to collect personal information from anyone who is under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13 you should not provide any personal information to us and you should use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and suspect he/she has provided personal information on or through the website, please contact us as set forth below under the section entitled “How Can I Contact You Regarding This Privacy Policy?”How do we keep personal information secure?The security of your information is very important to us. We have instituted several measures and security procedures to protect our servers and networks that store personal information. However, no transmission of information over the Internet is 100% secure and, therefore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information. In order to help protect personal information you provide to us: (i) you should not share your password or account information with anyone else, (ii) you should use a secure web browser, and (iii) you should change your password often. If you wish to cancel a password, or if you become aware of any loss, theft, or unauthorized use of a password, please contact us as set forth below under “How Can I Contact You Regarding This Privacy Policy?”How can I access, correct, and update personal information?You may access, correct and update certain personal information that you have provided to us by contacting us with your request as set forth below under the section entitled “How Can I Contact You Regarding This Privacy Policy?”We reserve the right to retain any personal information reasonably necessary to appropriately document our business activities and for record retention purposes. We will store personal information for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. You may find out more details regarding this Privacy Policy by contacting us as provided below under “How Can I Contact You Regarding This Privacy Policy?”What happens when I link to or from another site?This website may contain links to or from websites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply (“Linked Websites”). Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not reflect the practices regarding information collection, use and disclosure of Linked Websites or the owners or operators of those Linked Websites. Your use of Linked Websites will be governed by the terms of use, privacy policies, and other terms, notices, and policies set forth or referenced in those Linked Websites. We encourage you to be aware that when you leave this website you should read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit to ensure protection of your information.How can I contact you regarding this privacy policy?If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy or the Privacy Policy you can send a request with your concerns or any further questions to us by using the contact information provided below:By Email:https://www.savortheband.com/contact/ or contact@www.savortheband.com Subject: Privacy Policy QuestionsBy Mail: Savor the Band 11956 Bernardo Plaza Dr., #149, San Diego, CA 92128What if I am an international user?Our digital operations are conducted, in whole or in part, in the United States. Regardless of where you live, you consent to have your personal data transferred, processed, and stored in the United States, and allow SAVOR THE BAND use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.". . . a fabulous, high-energy performance."— Vicki GilkeyEvent ProducerCRA Los Angeles
